schiit.com 2019-08-25

# Terms | Schiit Audio

**Yeah, more lawyer stuff…**

But hey, you probably want to know what we do with your information. In reality, it is being collected, collated, and transmitted to a massive alien entity somewhere near Aldeberan which is contemplating a wholesale invasion of the Earth.

No, not really. Bottom line, we take great care with your information. We use PayPal for transaction processing, and we do not store credit card numbers on the site. And you’ll never get email from us unless you sign up via the “Spam” link at the top of the page. And even then, it’ll be very infrequent. We aren’t like some of these guys who send three newsletters a week. More like three a year.

If you want the full lawyer version, read on.

**How do we get your information?**  
When you purchase something from us, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.

When you browse our site, we automatically receive your computer’sinternet protocol (IP) address, and information about your browser and operating system.

Finally, when you sign up for our “Spam”, we take your email address.

**What do you do with it?**  
We use personal information from your purchase to complete the transaction via PayPal, using the PayPal API. For information on their security procedures, please refer to PayPal.

We use your IP address and browser information in analytics, but we don’t pay much attention to them, really.

We use your Email from the “Spam” link to send you, well, spam. We do not resell this list, nor provide it to any partners or third parties.

**How do you get my consent to use this information?**   
When you give us personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, or return a purchase, you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

When your sign up for our “Spam,” you’re consenting to us sending you periodic emails.

**How do I withdraw my consent?**   
If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, by contacting us at [[email protected]](https://www.schiit.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Disclosure**  
We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

**Third-party Services**  
We use PayPal for transaction processing, as well as USPS and FedEx for shipping. We recommend that you read their privacy policies to understand how your personal information will be handled by them. Please note that transactions using third parties are subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

**Links**  
When you click on links on our site, they may cause you to leave our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites.

**Security**  
To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

**Changes to this privacy policy**  
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently.

**Questions and contact information**  
If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, contact [[email protected]](https://www.schiit.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
